[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":152434,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":163956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":29203,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":193162,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":44438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":237603,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2335,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":239940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":245082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2776,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":247860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the sec ond one  to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4837,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":252698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1729,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":254428,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":258219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1150,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":259371,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":264259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<su b>6</sub > 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1198,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":265458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":268170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1289,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":269460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br / > (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2900,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":272362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1127,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":273490,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your r esult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2680,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":276171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1166,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":277338,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6751,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":284090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1095,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":285186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2822,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":288010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1350,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":289362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":41893,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":331258,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own i nverse u nder +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":39975,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":371234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":7559,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":378794,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1319,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":380114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br / > (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":382722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":911,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":383635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":386042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":387466,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":389994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity unde r +<sub> 6</sub>.","rt":1079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":391074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":393802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3919,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":397722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simp ly be pe rformed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":8727,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":406450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub > 2, but  there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":92247,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":498698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":8687,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":507386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1959,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":509346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Rememb er, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":511771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":26174,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":537947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub> ? <br /> <br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":26469,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":564419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1424,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":565852,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":570475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1486,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":571963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make  sure yo u understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":12478,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":584443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":589667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1246,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":590915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6 "],"rt":4708,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":595627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5140,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":600770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4961,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":605732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":609578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":613482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":8968,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":622451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4  +<sub>9< /sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"you add four plus one it equals to less than nine so the answer is five. ","explanation_history":["you add 4 plus ","you add 4 ","you add 4","you add ","you add four plus one it equlas to less than nine so the answer is five. ","you add four plus one it equals to less than nine so the answer is five. "],"response_history":["5"],"rt":47556,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":670010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"you add eight plus four which equals twelve. since twelve is greater than nine you subtract nine and get the answer three. ","explanation_history":["you ad d eight  plus four which eqauls ","you add eight plus four which eqauls","you add eight plus four which eqaul","you add eight plus four which eqau","you add eight plus four which eqa","you add eight plus four which equals twelve. so","you add eight plus four which equals twelve. since twelve is greater than nine you subtract nine and get the anse","you add eight plus four which equals twelve. since twelve is greater than nine you subtract nine and get the answer three. "],"response_history":["3"],"rt":58166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":728178,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"zero is the identity number because it gives the  identical number back.","explanation_history":["zero is the identity number because anything you ad d to it  ","zero is the identity number because anything you add to it","zero is the identity number because anything you add to i","zero is the identity number because anything you add to ","zero is the identity number because anything you add to","zero is the identity number because anything you add t","zero is the identity number because anything you add ","zero is the identity number because anything you add","zero is the identity number because anything you ad","zero is the identity number because anyt","zero is the identity number because any","zero is the identity number because an","zero is the identity number because a","zero is the identity number because ","zero is the identity number becausethe identical number back.","zero is the identity number because identical number back.","zero is the identity number because  identical number back.","zero is the identity number because i identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it identical number back.","zero is  the ide ntity number because it  identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it g identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gi identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it giv identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it give identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gives identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gives  identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gives t identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gives th identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gives the identical number back.","zero is the identity number because it gives the  identical number back."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":116608,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":844787,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"the inverse of a number is the element  you combine with it to get the identity ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["it is the number you combine with it to get the number. ","it is the number you combine with it to get the n","the inverse of a number is the number you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the e you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the el you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the ele you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the elem you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the eleme you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the elemen you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the element you combine with it to get the identity ","the inverse of a number is the  element   you combine with it to get the identity "],"rt":148269,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":993058,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":38441,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1031500,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":7331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1038834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your ans wer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"if you add three and six together it equals nine. so six is the inverse under three","explanation_history":["if you add three and six together it equals nine. so six is the inverse under three"],"response_history":["6"],"rt":51368,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1090203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because if you add every number under nine to two then it would not equal nine. ","explanation_history":["because if you add every number under nine to two then it would not equal nine. "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":91366,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1181572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"because if you add three plus three plus three it equals nine you can generate the number with three. ","explanation_history":["because if you add 3","because if you add three plus three plus three it equals nine you can generate the number with three. "],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":94622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1276196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you cannot generate nine by adding five and five. ","explanation_history":["no","n","because you cannot generate nine by adding five and five. "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":30883,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1307082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"because you cannot make every other number using just six. ","explanation_history":["because you cannot make evry","because you cannot make evr","because you cannot make every other number using just six. "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":112769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1419853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other cou nting nu mber you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":11916,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1431771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"the number you combine with +n to equal one. ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["the number you combine with +n to equal 1. ","the number you combine with +n to equal 1.","the number you combine with +n to equal 1","the number you combine with +n to equal ","the number you combine with +n to equal one. so in this case 1+n=1","the number you combine with +n to equal one. so in this case 1+n=","the number you combine with +n to equal one. so in this case 1+n","the number you combine with +n t o equal  one. so","the number you combine with +n to equal one. s","the number you combine with +n to equal one. "],"rt":216116,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1647891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x","explain":true,"explanation":"because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse   of the element. ","explanation_history":["because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse for the ","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse for the","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse for th","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse for t","because if you add x to +n the answer  must be  x because that is the inverse for ","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse for","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse fo","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse f","because if you add x to +n the answer must be x because that is the inverse   of the element. "],"response_history":["x"],"rt":229117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1877010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"you would have to see if x equals every other number under +n. ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["beca","bec","be","b","you would have to see  if x equ als every other number under +n. "],"rt":55280,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1932292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":33733,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1966026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False","True","False"],"rt":9391,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1975418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":9406,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1984826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"if x is a multiple of +n it would be a generator. ","explanation_history":["if x is a multiple of +n it would be a generator. "],"response_history":["False"],"rt":52125,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2036954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":33614,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2070570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"because if x is a generator under +n then it will always equal a numbe r less t han +n","explanation_history":["because if x is a geb","because if x is a generator under +n then it will always equal a number less than +n"],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":73751,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2144322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":8783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2153106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2168,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2155275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"44","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["44"],"rt":2782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2158059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":4341,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2162402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced mat h class  you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"algebra2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["algebra!!","algebra!","algebra2"],"rt":13921,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2176324,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it","4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":13053,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2189380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":11068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2200451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2204730,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2207858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2211922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Female"],"rt":2311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2214234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":6431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2220666,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes ","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["yes "],"rt":6696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2227363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"it was difficult but I really enjoyed it, thank you!!!!","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["it was du","it was difficult but I really enjoyed it, thank you!!!!"],"rt":20718,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2248083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]